Angel (Angi) Wang | LinkedIn 9/6/18, 6:31 PM

Deadline Approaching Soon - Syracuse's online Master of Science in Data Science. GRE waivers available. 廣告 …



Angel (Angi) Wang • 3 度

Data Scientist at Expedia, Inc.

美國 大西雅圖地區

傳送訊息



Expedia, Inc.



University of Washington



查看聯絡資料



Aspiring Data Scientist with four-year proficiency in data analysis, statistical modelling, project management, and translating statistical results into business recommendations. Industry experience in R and Python for writing machine-learning algorithms, SQL for database querying, Hive/Hadoop for distributed computing, and Tableau for generating visualizations.



工作經歷



Data Scientist

Expedia, Inc. 2018年1月-目前・9個月

Bellevue, WA



Data Science Intern

Expedia, Inc.

2017年6月-2017年9月 · 4個月

Bellevue, WA

- Loaded and modeled Expedia booking data in Hadoop, and processed the data for analysis to answer customer service experience questions.
- Developed, implemented and tested statistical models using R (caret, party, tree, mboost, e1071, rpart, etc.) and Python (SciKit-Learn, TensorFlow, Scrapy, etc.) to show how booking variables impact customer service contact behavior and recommended business solution to deflect customer service contact and provide effortless customer
- Project: Developed predictive customer service call models utilizing 23M Expedia 2016 booking transaction and contact data. Three predictive models were built and tested in R and Python: identifying likely callers, predicting caller window and caller need. Proposed initiatives on service call reduction and customer segmentation, using personalized experience based on insights from analysis. 收回



Data Analyst Intern





廣告 ...

Yu-Ting, 看看Expedia Group有沒有適 合你的職缺

杳看職缺

您可能也想看看



Yue(Rania) Zheng • 3 度 Data Scientist II at Expedia, Inc.



Yiyun Peng • 3 度 Sr. Data Scientist at Expedia, Inc.

Ian Liu Data Scientist at Expedia



Xin Xin • 3 度 Statistician/Data Scientist II at Expedia, Inc.



Chuchu Bai • 3 度 Data Scientist



Shervin Minaee • 3 度 Data Scientist at Expedia Group



Congrui Yi • 3 度 Data Scientist at Expedia, Inc.



Samira Daruki • 3 度 Applied Research Scientist at Expedia, Inc.



Yufei(Ricky) Yue • 3 度 Data Scientist at Expedia, Inc.



Sophia Chang Liu • 3 度 Data Scientist at Microsoft Angel (Anqi) Wang | LinkedIn 9/6/18, 6:31 PM



UW Medicine

2016年9月-2017年6月 · 10個月

Seattle, WA

- Conducted statistical analysis on employee on-boarding survey data to generate predictive analysis trends using Excel and R. Produced and presented reports, using PowerPoint and Word, to senior leadership in HR to improve employee satisfaction.
- Provided administrative support and managed record maintenance based on established retention schedules for HR.

收回



Private Banker

Wells Fargo

2015年1月-2016年6月·1年6個月

Seattle, WA

- Advised clients on wealth management at a monetary threshold of \$1M per quarter.
- Tailored portfolios catering to clients' financial status, objective, risk tolerance, tax exposure and investment goals.
- Leveraged computational analytics to devise accurate projections of portfolio returns for clients.
- Experienced advisor on Mutual Funds, Stocks, Fixed Income, Bonds, CDs, ETFs, Options, Annuities.

收回



Business Analyst

Expeditors

2014年1月-2014年12月・12個月

Greater Seattle Area

- Analyzed client logistics data to support senior management in devising strategic plans for Q1 2015.
- Coordinated cross-team operations to streamline efficiency across all product lines, reducing headcount by 20%.
- Proposed solutions aligned with customer needs and increased satisfaction by 7% in Q4 2014. 收回

https://www.linkedin.com/in/angel-wang/?lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad_fl...n%3Ali%3Acontrol%3Ad_flagship3_profile_view_base-browsemap_profile

教育背景



University of Washington

Master of Science (MSc), Data Science, 3.91 2016年-2018年



University of Washington

Bachelor's degree, Statistics; Economics; Mathematics 2010年-2013年

技能和肯定

Data Analysis · 17



🕎 誰給肯定: Tianchang (Jack) Liu和其他 3 人(也擅長此技能)

Microsoft Office · 17



🚹 誰給肯定: Angel (Jiangyun) Zhu (也擅長此技能)

Microsoft Excel · 15

促銷內容



Syracuse Online Master's

Gain programming skills and interpret data with a master's in data science

深入瞭解



Managers and Executives

Supercharge your leadership skills with an MBA from top CEO Jack Welch.

深入瞭解

Angel (Anqi) Wang | LinkedIn 9/6/18, 6:31 PM

誰給肯定: Angel (Jiangyun) Zhu (也擅長此技能)

展開 ~

個人成就

9 門課程

Applied Regression and Analysis of Variance • Applied Statistics and Experimental Design • Computational Finance and Financial Econometrics • Data Management for Data Science • Data Visualization & Experimental Design • Investment, Capital, and Finance • Scalable Data Systems & Algorithms • Statistical Machine Learning • Statistics Software Applications

5 個測驗成績

Society of Actuary Exam MFE Financial Economics • Society of Actuary VEE Applied Statistics • Society of Actuary VEE Economics • Society of Actuary Exam FM/2 Financial Mathematics • Society of Actuary Exam P/1 Probability

3 語言能力

Chinese • English • Japanese

1 獲頒專利

Interactive Multi-media Presentation System and its working platform

